[Music]
hi i'm avinash i have a superpower
i'm bringing the world-class technology
at your doorstep
with most accuracy representing icncl
lumbar
world-class technology icr ocr smart way
of booking policies
[Music]
log into the digital server portal
go to iso command
and click on to get code
[Music]
you now will see the landing page
click on croc
and then upload either rc or policy
once the policy is successfully uploaded
search
for the uploaded policy using promenades
click on edit
review the policy details
vehicle debates
customer details
and make the payment
benefits of icr ocr reduce turnaround
time
less effort no manual entry
better accuracy
do not upload the images
that are
blind
background noise crumbled
faded flash on skill
watery
incomplete
having icr technology will not only
speed up processing time but also reduce
errors lessen time spent revealing and
fixing errors
[Music]